♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Is Netflix Streaming
the right choice for you?
Well, if you like movies in HD,
then frozen pixels, then HD again,
the answer is "yes."
And if you love the golden
year of movies, 2003,
then we might have some of
what you're looking for.
Netflix Streaming:
buffer for 20 minutes,
then watch 35 minutes of a
movie with Jason Statham.
Oh, look what came,
the free DVD from my PBS pledge.
Whatever it is, we're not watching it.
Peter, trust me,
you of all people could really
learn something from this.
It's a documentary about
the food industry called,
Food Kills.
Huh. Says here that
Colon Health Magazine
gave it two thumbs in.
Hi, I'm Matt Lauer's
cousin, Stephen McCormick.
Our moms are sisters.
America is gorging itself
on processed food,
creating an obesity epidemic.
We've abandoned natural foods
for chemicals, additives
and refined sugars.
At this rate, this is what
the future will look like.
Those are flying cars,
but the people in them are too fat.
Oh, no, I left my baby in there.
Without drastic changes in our diet,
Americans are headed for
a health catastrophe.
For more, go to our website at
"double-u double-u
double-u dot PBS dot com."
That's "www" dot,
the word "double-u" three times,
the word "dot," "PBS,"
the word "dot" again,
the word "com," dot com.
There was a miscommunication
when we registered our website.
Well, that's it, from now on,
we're eating healthy around here.
We're gonna feel better and
we're gonna look better.
Well, looking better doesn't
always solve your problems, Lois.
It sure didn't work for Droopy
Dog when he got that facelift.
Contrary to my appearance,
I'm still not happy.
Please study my brain so that
others don't suffer as I have.
Thanks for coming to my
birthday party, you guys.
And Esther, I'm so sorry
you ripped your perineum
doing the Hokey Pokey.
That's okay, I got free curly fries.
Okay, let's see what Meg got me.
A crock pot?
Things about to get crazy!
You can cook a pork
tenderloin under your bed.
Excuse me, girls.
We're about to start
roller derby in a minute.
Wait, wait.
You. What's your name?
Me? Meg Griffin.
Would you mind standing up?
Whoa! What-what-what are you doing?
My God.
The magic ratio.
What's that?
It means your ankles, calves, and thighs
are all the same thickness.
How would you like to try out
for the roller derby team?
Really?
- Do it, Meg.
- Yeah, Meg. You should totally do it.
Meg's talking to a boy!
Okay, sure. What the heck?
Here. Take my card.
"I am a registered sex offender."
Flip it over.
see other side."
Give me that.
I'm the roller derby coach.
See you at tryouts.
I can't believe it, you guys.
This is the biggest surprise
since the last M. Night Shyamalan movie.
Two tickets for the M.
Night Shyamalan movie.
Wow. Really?
Hope you guys are ready
for a healthy dinner.
I went to Whole Foods
today and got this recipe
from an extremely thin man
with a giant Adam's apple.
I hate that place.
None of the cereals
are advertised on TV.
What's this stuff that looks like sand?
It's quinoa.
Nope, I don't eat foods that
sound like karate words.
Well, according to Food
Kills, quinoa is a superfood.
It's very nutritious, and it
even helps keep you regular.
Lois, I have a system...
I poop once a week for
an hour and a half.
I wear a headband and it's
soaked when I'm all done.
Mm.
Wow, Lois, you know, this
is actually pretty good.
Peter, you should try it.
Ugh. Fine.
Peter, knock it off.
I can't help it!
My body's rejecting it!
Name?
Quinoa.
Mm-hmm.
Sorry, sir, we're full.
Come on in, gummy bears!
Oh, you are looking fine tonight.
Mm!
Thanks again for coming
and supporting me, Chris.
No problem. And I'm gonna
take some pictures
of the other athletes,
if you don't mind.
You might not know this about me,
but I am a bit of a shutterbug.
Okay, that's-that's all okay.
All right, ladies, line up.
How about we start with some warm-ups?
Bend down and touch your toes.
"Memory card full"?
Come on!
Okay, now, last year we were tricked
by a couch on a dolly with wheels,
so if any of you is a couch
on a dolly with wheels,
I'm gonna ask you to please leave now.
Well, we need five for a team
and there's five of you here,
so congratulations.
Wow! This is awesome!
I can't believe I'm a Quahog Thug!
When do we start skating?
Here, look at the schedule.
This is just a list of
Sexaholic Anonymous meetings.
Flip it over.
It says, "Remember to
attend your meetings."
I'm gonna stop handing you stuff.
It's the middle of the night.
Where are you going?
I'm sick of all this healthy crap.
I'm going downstairs to
find something good to eat.
And then I'm gonna fall asleep
watching transvaginal mesh
lawsuit commercials.
There's nothing.
Thank you, son.
What's going on, man, are you pregnant?
No, my wife watched
that food documentary.
And you should never ask that
unless you're sure, by the way.
Aw, yeah, peanut-butter-cup-
Dorito-sausage-car panini.
And let's crack a Cadbury
Egg over the whole thing.
Just gonna use my spare
glove-compartment-underwear
as a napkin.
I can't believe Randy Quaid gets
to eat like this every day.
Peter? Is that you?
Cleveland?
Are you cooking in your car?
I am.
Is this because of Food Kills?
Oh, you saw that movie too, huh?
We watched Tyler Perry's Food Kills,
which is the same movie except it stars
black folks you've never heard of
and white folks you don't
hear from anymore.
But, yeah, now Donna is
forcing me to eat healthy.
I always get confused,
is Donna the wife,
or is Roberta the wife?
I don't know, man, can I
have some of that sandwich?
Oh, our hands just touched.
Mm.
Wow, Peter. That's good.
That's real good.
I'm not sure what we're doing now.
Excuse me,
whatever you've got in
there smells incredible.
Man, my wife won't let me
eat any of that stuff.
Tell you what, I'll give you
ten bucks for that thing.
Yeah, me, too.
Wow.
Huh, if I sell two
sandwiches for $10 each,
that equals...
money.
Peter, you just made $20
from two sandwiches.
Wow, you're right.
Hey, maybe I could turn
this into a business.
You know, selling sandwiches from a car.
Wonder how much I could make.
♪ Mad world... ♪
Whoops, I stopped thinking about math
and started thinking about
baby-man Billy Corgan
being sad at Disneyland.
Peter, what the hell is this?
This, Lois, is my new food truck,
specializing in all the
delicious, unhealthy foods
that you won't let me eat.
'Cause you don't let me
eat what I want to eat
and that... and, uh, I am super dizzy
and there might be a gas
leak in this thing.
I can't believe you'd buy a food truck.
What are you even selling?
First of all, believe it, baby.
Second, uh, mostly hamburgers
where the buns is jelly donuts.
And drinks where hot dogs is the straws.
Mm.
Another milkshake, please.
Look, I'm happy for the business,
but drinking that on your knees is...
it's putting a hat on a hat.
Look at this food. It's
gross and unhealthy.
It's exactly the stuff I'm
trying to get you not to eat.
Yeah, but people like this
food. It makes them happy.
I mean, you can eat sprouts and
vegan crap your entire life
and still get devoured by Gremlins
and-and-and none of it matters.
So you're saying you shouldn't
take care of yourself
because you might get
devoured by Gremlins?
Get a clue, mama.
Think of what you're doing
to your body, Peter.
Oh, there we go.
You think I'm overweight.
I know you're overweight.
Hey, yeah, I'll have the,
uh, Swedish Fish Tacos.
You want the can of chili
dumped on top or on the side?
What does the chef recommend?
Me? I like to squeeze the can so hard
the chili flies into
my mouth like Popeye.
Do it up.
You got it. Let me put on my bandana,
fire up my very loud "what"
generator, and get cooking.
Peter, this isn't over!
What?!
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the first bout of the season,
the Quahog Thugs versus
the Medford Dump Cakes.
This season we're brought to
you by Barry's Note Cards.
"When you need to remind
yourself of the sponsor,
use Barry's Note Cards."
Nice move, Griffin.
Way to go, Meg!
Wow, newcomer Meg Griffin
is lighting up the track
with some amazing moves.
"Amazing"? Damn right, amazing.
Make some noise
if you're mixing prescription
drugs with alcohol!
Wow. This is a lot more
physical than I thought.
My favorite part of a
woman's body is haunches.
And this is all haunch, baby.
Meg!
Boy, that was rough.
This sport's even more
dangerous than skeet shooting.
Pull!
I got in the wrong line!
That'll be $16.
$16? That's expensive.
Yes, sir. Everything's very expensive
because you're paying for it on an iPad.
Now, if you'll just select a gratuity.
Options are 60%, 90%, and 200%.
Uh, I guess 60%.
Okay, great.
And just sign by dragging
your bare finger
across this thing I use to masturbate.
Uh, okay.
Thank you, please make sure
to bang your head on
that low-hanging thing.
What are you...
Oh, you spilled something.
You want a napkin?
Yes, please.
All right, here's 40, blown by the wind.
Oh, Chris, I'm glad you're here.
Swing that lamp at me.
But you'll get hurt.
No, I won't.
I'm gonna dodge it.
Oh, my God, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
This roller derby's
really toughened me up.
I got to say, I've-I've
never felt better.
Really?
'Cause I watched how rough it
was out there the other day,
and I got a little worried for you.
I mean, all it would take is one bad hit
to do permanent damage.
I think you should quit.
What? No.
No, I-I love roller derby.
It's the first thing I'm really good at.
Plus, I love making other women bleed.
But you know, in ways besides the way,
you know, they normally bleed.
She means periods.
Yeah, I got it, Stewie,
but I'm telling you, Meg,
something bad is going to happen.
Like when you give a young
athlete too much money.
I, I got to murder somebody.
Peter, kids, dinner!
Kids? Peter?
It's time for a healthy, veggie dinner!
Come on, I spent the whole day
making the house smell like farts.
Where the hell is everybody?
All right, I got a bowl of cereal
that's M&M's and Dr. Pepper?
Over here.
Chris, put that down.
You kids get in the house
and eat the healthy dinner I prepared,
and Peter, you, too.
Shut down that truck and get inside.
Lois, I already told you.
I don't want to eat your
garbage food. All right?
Now can you go inside and
get me some Pop Rocks?
I'm making a paella.
You know what? Enough of this nonsense.
You love this truck so much, stay in it,
'cause I don't want you or
your food in the house.
Fine. I love this truck.
I got everything I need in here.
Maybe I'll just live here.
I can imagine it now.
♪ Living in America... ♪
Whoops. I stopped
thinking about the truck
and started thinking about Amazon woman
Brigitte Nielsen drunk
in a Burbank park.
All right, time to greet the day.
Are you living in a truck?
Not bad. I see you got a
Hooters calendar in here.
How do you get anything done
with those rocking
knockers staring at you?
Hey, who says I get anything done?
Guy talk, guy talk. Yeah, guy talk.
Guy talk. This is how guys talk.
Oh, Peter, this is awful.
Well, I love it.
And I'm not going back in that house
and listen to Lois tell me
how fat and unhealthy I am.
You do look like you've put on a few.
Your elbows are starting to pucker.
Yeah, I mean, are you
really happy in here?
You bet I am.
I'm happier than a squash on Halloween.
Dad, are they coming
to take us away, too?
No, son, we're fine.
How about on Thanksgiving?
You know what, just enjoy the month.
You're going down, Griffin,
like my stepfather's pants!
I guess I see where some
of your anger comes from.
Oh, no. This is bad.
That's it. I have to do something.
Chris, what are you doing?
Saving my...
Oh, my God. Chris, are you okay?
I don't think so. I'm hurt pretty bad,
like that time I was
running with scissors.
You run like a girl.
Run like a man, you get a suit.
Here you go. And if you'd
like to put your e-mail
on our sign-up list,
I'd be happy to sell
it to Russian hackers.
Peter, Peter, it's happening.
What? The Bing Maps car.
It's three blocks down and
it's coming this way.
Holy crap. This is the day
we've been waiting for.
We said we're gonna stand
in our front yards
and wave as it goes by so
we're on the street view.
We're gonna be on the Internet.
Mort just called. It went by his house.
Everybody, places! Start waving.
This is not a drill!
Damn it. I can't fit through the door.
I'm stuck in the truck.
What? What are you talking about?
I knew this would happen.
You're too fat to get out.
I see it. I see the Bing car.
Oh, my God, Bing! Bing! Over here! Bing!
They can't see you, Peter.
You're facing away from the street.
Stop talking, Quagmire. Just smile.
This is amazing.
Crap. Is it gone?
The driver nodded at me.
I... I think I'm gonna cry.
Damn it. I can't believe I missed it.
Jeez, I hope I don't
end up stuck in here
like Winnie the Pooh.
Uh, Rabbit?
Perhaps you should push with
your shoulder and not your fist?
Don't worry about it.
Hey, did that big "boomba
boomba" nurse come in here?
Uh, no.
But Dr. Hartman, is my
brother gonna be okay?
That's her. That's her.
Hi, Juanita.
Hello, Doctor.
Was that weird? Was I just weird?
Kind of.
You don't know. I was fine.
Oh, Chris, I'm so sorry
you got hurt like this.
Roller derby was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
I finally felt like I was good
at something, I made friends...
but seeing you like this,
I realize you were right.
It's too dangerous.
So I'm going to quit.
No, Meg. I got hurt because
I didn't belong out there,
but you do.
I watched you skate.
You found your calling
and I believe in you.
Now get back to that
rink and help your team
win the championship it deserves.
Really? I will. Thanks, Chris.
With the spirit in her heart renewed,
Meg returned to the roller derby arena.
I think she did all right,
but no one will know for
sure because halfway through
everyone stopped to watch some fat kid
who was killing it on
Dance Dance Revolution.
Dance, you fat bitch.
So tonight, we say to the
yellow-billed marsh finch...
you're extinct.
But, right now, we're getting
word of breaking news.
We go live to Tricia
Takanawa with details.
- Tricia?
- Tom, I'm standing here
outside a Spooner Street home,
where a local business owner
has apparently eaten himself
into his own food truck.
Oh. It appears they've
finally removed the roof.
Nobody look. This is a
private, gross matter.
Mr. Griffin, is this performance art
or, uh, some sort of
political statement?
Well, I'm kind of ticked
about condoms in porn,
but this is unrelated.
Oh, hey, Lois. I guess
you must be happy.
Yeah, it's every girl's dream
to have her husband hoisted
out of a food truck in a horse harness.
No, look, I-I'm just
saying, you were right.
I'm a big tub of lard,
and you have every reason
to be ashamed of me.
Ashamed of you?
I-Is that really what you think?
Well, yeah, you kept saying
how overweight I am.
Peter, don't you get it?
I only wanted you to eat
healthy because I love you,
and I'm concerned about your health.
I want you around for
as long as I'm around.
Really? Well, I love you, too, Lois.
I'm sorry I was such a jerk.
I guess I could do without
eating so much junk,
but I could never do without you.
Oh, Peter.
Ma'am, please step back.
We have to wash him with a hose.
Guys, look! Look! The Bing car is back.
No. I'm not ready! I'm not ready!
Inspired by his love for Lois,
Peter had steamed vegetables
and brown rice that evening,
then ate like crap for
the rest of his life.
Nonetheless, he was
immortalized on Bing Maps.
Fat people are amusing to me.
Hang there, you fat bitch.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru